[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This fish, which resembles the Angel fish, is recognized by its brightly coloured and patterned body, as well as by the dark band across its eyes.", "correct_answer": "Butterfly fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Purple queen", "Cichlid", "Clown fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food is the French delicacy called Andouillette?", "correct_answer": "Sausage", "incorrect_answers": ["Cheese", "Salted fish", "Mussel soup"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who drew the first pollitical cartoon published in an American newspaper?", "correct_answer": "Ben Franklin", "incorrect_answers": ["Samuel Freeman", "Dr. Seuss", "Thomas Nast"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Major League Baseball, who was the first pitcher to win 200 games in his career?", "correct_answer": "A.G.Spaulding", "incorrect_answers": ["Walter Johnson", "Cy Young", "Babe Ruth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does Walter break his leg in the comedy film Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead?", "correct_answer": "Falling off the roof", "incorrect_answers": ["Car accident", "Ice-Skating", "Playing football"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What music is playing when the Captain stands for the first time in the movie WALL-E?", "correct_answer": "2001 A Space Odyssey", "incorrect_answers": ["The Ascent of Man", "Rocky movie theme", "Gonna Fly Now"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What medical condition do prunes and prune juice relieve?", "correct_answer": "Constipation", "incorrect_answers": ["Dizziness", "Pain", "Cramps"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This name, most popular in the 80s and 90s, means wealth, but also clairvoyance or foresight.", "correct_answer": "Jessica", "incorrect_answers": ["Miranda", "Sarah", "Kristen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fabric hook-and-loop fasteners with the brand name, Velcro, were invented by Swiss engineer Georges de Mestral in what year?", "correct_answer": "1948", "incorrect_answers": ["1969", "1960", "1965"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the anvil-shaped bone in the middle ear that along with the malleus and stapes allow us to hear?", "correct_answer": "Incus", "incorrect_answers": ["Incense", "Inca", "Inuit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 23rd US President was in office during this period.", "correct_answer": "1889 - 1893", "incorrect_answers": ["1909 - 1913", "1837 - 1841", "1877 - 1881"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie is Friday character Mr. Jones watching when he asks Craig to bring him some water?", "correct_answer": "Mans Best Friend", "incorrect_answers": ["All Dogs Go to Heaven", "Mr. Post Man", "Help Me Please!"]}]